on some.
I'm certainly not currently going to avoid it,
but I'm hoping it meets our needs
and I know that the executive is hoping that as well.
Is there anything else that stands out to you or anything else you want to touch on from
the last four years?
The executive understands our retention issues with support staff and APAs,
so we're working on that as we speak.
So the retention issues,
it's being able to,
we want career prosecutors,
we want, we eventually want to have a staff,
not want, we eventually need to have a staff.
This is representative of what this county is and in the executive knows,
and I think everybody knows,
I've been talking about it for years,
that when it comes to kind of our size,
we are again severely understaffed,
but we're getting there,
we're working toward that goal.
As long as I see some progress,
then I'm happy with the leadership that we're having.
And again,
he gets what we need.
And when I call him,
he picks up the phone and me turns my calls.
And then addresses those concerns.
And so I would like to think that he feels the same way about this office,
that I will address the concerns that he has.
And I'm very pleased with those things that have happened so far.
But Wayne County is a place where I'm raising my children,
where my office is,
where our constituencies is,
we want it to be safe first and foremost, my overriding concern.
For not only myself,
not only for my family,
not only for my staff,
but for the community that we serve is that we can be safe,
a progressive place,
a place that's not afraid to address any issues in the criminal justice system,
and at the end of the day,
it's a safe place to live, work,
worship, and live.
And one last thing I forget.
I should probably say that it's a safe place to live,
work, worship, and play.
And the one last thing I would say is I remember when I came on board about two and a half years ago,
and I remember looking back at what it had done in the first year or so,
as I'm trying to get up the speed, I remember.
And his first budget,
he was able to give a car about $1 million for the backlog of the red kids.
That was it.
For that to occur at a time when you're making a lot of difficult financial decisions.
When
I first met with the CEO about when he was declaring his candidacy,
and I met with him to talk about whether I was going to support him or not.
And there were several things that were deal-breakers for me.
And I knew that I had to have some support for the main issues of the office.
One of those main issues was we had no previous support from the previous administration for the sexual assault case that had been discovered in 2009.
The others were things I've talked about already.
They were...